Guide to the League of Women Voters of the City of New York Records
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
League of Women Voters of the City of New York Records,
1919-1979.
League of Women Voters of the City of New York.
60,000 items (139 boxes, 6 v., 1 oversize)
Columbia University. Rare Book and Manuscript Library, New York, NY.
4079018
History
Scope and Content
Correspondence, memoranda, minutes, reports, scrapbooks, printed material, and photographs. The files contain much material of the League of Women Voters of New York State as well, and some material pertaining to the national organization. The files document the League's activities in the areas of voter registration, election reform, New York City government, foreign policy, ecology, and numerous other concerns, and contain the records of city, state, and national conventions, annual reports, and Board and Council minutes. Major correspondents include Emanuel Teller, Stanley M. Isaacs, Jacob K. Javits, Robert F. Kennedy, Edward I. Koch, John Vliet Lindsay, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Anna Lord Strauss, and Percy E. Sutton.
Subjects
League of Women Voters of New York State.; Celler, Emanuel, 1888-1981.; Isaacs, Stanley M. (Stanley Myer), 1882-1962.; Javits, Jacob K. (Jacob Koppel), 1904-1986.; Kennedy, Robert F., 1925-1968.; Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich), 1908-1979.; Koch, Ed, 1924-; Lindsay, John V. (John Vliet); United States--Foreign relations.; New York (N.Y.)--Politics and government--1898-1951.; New York (N.Y.)--Politics and government--1951-; New York (State)--Politics and government--1865-1950.; New York (State)--Politics and government--1951-; Ecology--New York (State); Voter registration--New York (State)--New York.; Voter registration--New York (State); Elections--Corrupt practices.; Women--New York (State)--New York--Societies and clubs.; Women--New York (State)--Societies and clubs.; Social problems.; Women in politics.; Photoprints.; Scrapbooks.
Acquisition
1955 M-55 League of Women Voters of the City of New York Gift
- Series I: Correspondence
  - Abzug, Bella S. (Box 1)
  - Koch, Edward I. (Box 1)
  - LaGuardia, Fiorello H. (Box 1)
  - Beame, Abraham D. (Box 1)
  - Lefkowitz, Louis J. (Box 1)
  - Belmont, Eleanor Robson (Box 1)
  - Lehman, Herbert H. (Box 1)
  - Buckley, James L. (Box 1)
  - Lindsay, John Vliet (Box 1)
  - Burlingham, Charles Culp (Box 1)
  - McCarthy, Eugene J. (Box 1)
  - Carey, Hugh L. (Box 1)
  - Morgenthau, Henry, Jr. (Box 1)
  - Carman, Harry J. (Box 1)
  - Moses, Robert (Box 1)
  - Celler, Emanuel (Box 1)
  - O'Dwyer, Paul (Box 1)
  - Cherne, Leo (Box 1)
  - Reid, Whitelaw (Box 1)
  - Chisholm, Shirley (Box 1)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Box 1)
  - Chute, Marchette (Box 1)
  - Rosenman, Samuel I. Roosevelt, Franklin D (Box 1)
  - Dewey, Thomas E. (Box 1)
  - Ruml, Beardsley (Box 1)
  - Douglas, Helen Gahagan (Box 1)
  - Seligman, Eustace (Box 1)
  - Dulles, John Foster (Box 1)
  - Smith, Alfred E. (Box 1)
  - Eisenhover, Mamie Doud (Box 1)
  - Strauss, Anna Lord (Box 1)
  - Fadiman, Clifton (Box 1)
  - Sutton, Percy E. (Box 1)
  - Gildersleeve, Virginia C. (Box 1)
  - Wagner, Robert F., Jr. (Box 1)
  - Harriman, William Averell (Box 1)
  - Wilson, Woodrow (Box 1)
  - Holtzman, Elizabeth (Box 1)
  - Isaacs, Stanley M. Hoover, Herbert Catalogued documents (Box 1)
  - Javits, Jacob K. (Box 1)
  - Keating, Kenneth B. Lindsay, John Vliet (Box 1)
  - Kennedy, Robert Wagner, Robert F., Jr. (Box 1)
  - Kenyon, Dorothy (Box 1)
  - Knopf, Alfred A. (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, Miscellaneous uncatalogued, 1934-1973 (Box 2)
- Series II: Files, A-Z
  - ABC (network) (Box 3)
  - Action Calls (Also called "Action" and "Time for Action;" includes some state and national materials) - 1954-1972. 11 Folders. (Box 3)
  - Active Voter, 1942-1973. 2 Folders (SEE ALSO Annual Reports - Public Relations (Box 3)
  - Annual Reports (SEE ALSO Reports - 1936-1939, 1952-1964 (Box 4)
  - Annual Reports, I964-1969 (Box 5)
  - Annual Reports, 1969-1972 (Box 6)
  - Annual Reports, Branch, 1953-1959 (Box 6)
  - Annual Reports, Branch, I96O-I965 (Box 7)
  - Annual Report Analyses, 1958-1963 (Box 7)
  - Annual Reports, Public Relations, 1963 - 1966 (Box 8)
  - Annual Reports, Public Relations, 1966-1970 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, Public Relations, 1972-1975 (Box 10)
  - Apportionment (includes headings: Reapportionment, Districting, Redistricting and Proportional Representation), 1930-1966. 7 Folders. (Box 10)
  - Apportionment, 1963-1971. 12 Folders (Box 11)
  - Backgroung Briefs, 1970-1971 (Box 11)
  - Baltimore Branch. 5 Folders (Box 11)
  - Benes Dinner, 1939 (Box 11)
  - Bicentennial Commission, 1973 (Box 11)
  - Birth Control, 1922-1935 (Box 11)
  - Board and Council Minutes, agendas and records, 1919-1926 (Box 12)
  - Board and Council Minutes, agendas and records, 1927-1940 (Box 13)
  - Board and Council Minutes, agendas and records (Box 14)
  - Board and Council Minutes, agendas and records, 1947-1953 (Box 15)
  - Board and Council Minutes, agendas and records, 1950-1956 (Box 16)
  - Board and Council Minutes, agendas and records, 1954-1959 (Box 17)
  - Board and Council Minutes, agendas and records, 1957-1968 (Box 18)
  - Board and Council Minutes, agendas and records, 1971-1973 (Box 19)
  - Branch, Floral Park (Box 20)
  - Branch, Metropolitan Evening (Box 20)
  - Branch, Staten Island (Box 20)
  - Branch Chairman's Workshop, 1959-1970 (Box 20)
  - Branch Problems, 1971 (Box 20)
  - Branches Outside New York (SEE ALSO Baltimore and Job Analyses) (Box 20)
  - By-Laws, 1924-1947 (Box 20)
  - By-Laws, 1970-1972. 2 Folders (Box 20)
  - Cable TV (Box 20)
  - Calendar, 1972-1973 (Box 20)
  - Catt, Carrie Chapman, Memorial Fund (Box 20)
  - China. 2 Folders (Box 20)
  - Christian Science Monitor (Box 20)
  - City Affairs (SEE ALSO Municipal Affairs and New York City) - Brochures (Box 20)
  - City Affairs, 1934-1953, 1945-1955 (Box 21)
  - City Affairs, 1953-1963. 4 Folders (Box 22)
  - City Almanac (Box 22)
  - City Lines (Box 22)
  - City Planning and Zoning, 1963-1973 (Box 22)
  - City Poll, 1953 (Box 22)
  - City Poll, 1956-1957. 4 Folders (Box 22)
  - City Poll, 1961 (Box 22)
  - Civic Affairs Forum, 1972 (Box 23)
  - Civic Assembly (Box 23)
  - Civic Participation Course - kit (Box 23)
  - Civil Rights (Box 23)
  - Civil Service. 3 Folders (Box 23)
  - Committee Reports, Miscellaneous, 1938-1952 (Box 23)
  - Community Development Article, 1971 (Box 23)
  - Community School Board Elections, 1973 (Box 23)
  - Congress, h Folders (Box 24)
  - Constitutional Convention, 1938-1953 (Box 24)
  - Constitutional Convention, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Constitutional Convention, 1966-1967. 4 Folders (Box 24)
  - Constitutional Convention, 1966-1967. 7 Folders (Box 25)
  - Consumer Department (Box 25)
  - Consumer Interest (Box 25)
  - Continuing Responsibilities (includes national materials). 2 Folders (Box 25)
  - Conventions (City), 1937 - 1947 (Box 26)
  - Conventions (City), 1948-1955 (Box 27)
  - Conventions (City) 1955-1967 (Box 28)
  - Conventions (City), 1968-1972 (Box 29)
  - Conventions (City), 1972-1973 (Box 30)
  - Council - SEE Board (Box 30)
  - County Government (Box 30)
  - Courts, Childrens, 1921-1942 (Box 30)
  - Courts, Family, 1964 (Box 30)
  - Courts, Citizens Conference on (Box 30)
  - Courts, New York State, 1955 (Box 30)
  - Courts, Trial by Jury (Box 30)
  - Current Agenda Proposals. 2 Folders (Box 30)
  - "Danger Confronting Popular Government" 1920 (Box 31)
  - Decentralization (Box 31)
  - Direct Line, 1963-1966 (Box 31)
  - Direct Line, 1972 (Box 31)
  - Districting - SEE Apportionment (Box 31)
  - Economic Policies, U.S. (Box 31)
  - Economic Policy Institute, 1961 (Box 31)
  - Economics, Domestic (Box 31)
  - Education, 1930-1969. 2 Folders (Box 31)
  - Education, 1970-. 2 Folders (Box 32)
  - Education – Board of Education (Box 32)
  - Education - Decentralization (Box 32)
  - Education Fund (Box 32)
  - Education - publications (miscellaneous; loose) (Box 32)
  - Education - publications (miscellaneous; loose) (Box 33)
  - Election Law - 1940-1969. 2 Folders (Box 33)
  - Election Law - Administration, 1969-1971 (Box 33)
  - Election Law - Direct Primary (Box 33)
  - Election Night Reporting, 1964 (Box 34)
  - Election Systems Project (Box 34)
  - Elections (Box 34)
  - Elections, 1969-1970 (Box 34)
  - Elections, 1971-1972 (Box 34)
  - Elections, 1973 (Box 34)
  - Elections, Primary, 1955-1968, 1973 (Box 34)
  - Electoral College (Box 34)
  - Environment, 1967-1973. 3 Folders. (SEE ALSO Water Resources) (Box 34)
  - Executive Interns, 1973 (Box 34)
  - Federal Loyalty/Security. 2 Folders (Box 35)
  - Field Secretary, 1959-1960 (Box 35)
  - Fiftieth Anniversary (Box 35)
  - Finances, 1961-1973. 3 Folders (Box 35)
  - Finances, Budgets, 1964-1971 (Box 35)
  - Finances, Policies (Box 35)
  - Finances — Publications (Box 36)
  - Finances — Skit, 1954 (Box 36)
  - Finances — Stockholders Reports, 1951-1958 (Box 36)
  - Finances — Tea, 1965-1966 (Box 36)
  - Flyers (Box 36)
  - Foreign Policy, 19^0-1955-3 Folders (Box 36)
  - Foreign Policy, 1959-1962 (Box 37)
  - Foreign Policy, 1971-1972 (Box 37)
  - Foreign Policy - Bricker Amendment (Box 37)
  - Foreign Policy - Connally Amendment (Box 37)
  - Foreign Policy - Economic (Box 37)
  - Foreign Policy - Publications (Box 37)
  - Foreign Policy Publications (Box 38)
  - Forest Hills, 1971 (Box 38)
  - Fortieth Anniversary, 1960 (Box 38)
  - Foundation for Citizen Education, 1971-1973 (Box 38)
  - Handbooks and Kits (also organization manuals) (Box 38)
  - Handbooks and Kits - City (Box 38)
  - Handbooks and Kits National (Box 39)
  - Harlem Unit&, 1956-1973. 2 Folders (Box 39)
  - Home Rule, 1936-1939 (Box 39)
  - Home Rule, District of Columbia (Box 39)
  - Hotels, 1972 (Box 39)
  - Housing, 1929-1971. 3 Folders (Box 40)
  - Human Resources, 1964-1973. 2 Folders (Box 40)
  - Industrial Relations (Box 4l)
  - International Relations (Box 4l)
  - International Woman Suffrage Alliance (Box 4l)
  - Job Analyses, 1953 Arlington, Va. (Box 4l)
  - Judicial System, 1958-1973. 3 Folders (Box 4l)
  - Jury Service (Box 42)
  - Juvenile Delinquency (Box 42)
  - Kits SEE (Box 42)
  - Handbooks (Box 42)
  - Kudos, 1973 (Box 42)
  - Labor SEE (Box 42)
  - Industrial Relations (Box 42)
  - Land Use (Box 42)
  - Legal Status (Box 42)
  - Legislative Programs (Box 42)
  - Legislative Conference, 1973 (Box 42)
  - Membership, 1948-1973. 4 Folders (Box 42)
  - Membership Cards (Box 43a)
  - Membership Cards (Box 43b)
  - Membership Cards (Box 43c)
  - Membership Cards (Box 44a)
  - Membership Cards (Box 44b)
  - Membership Cards (Box 44c)
  - Memoranda, Notes and Drafts (Box 45)
  - Men's Committee. 14 Folders (Box 45)
  - Metropolitan Project Survey, 1972-1973 (Box 46)
  - Municipal Affairs Committee, 1933-1938 (SEE ALSO City Affairs) (Box 46)
  - National (i.e., League of Women Voters of the United States, h Folders (Box 46)
  - National - Board Reports, 1969-1972 (Box 47)
  - National - Conventions, 1958-1968 (Box 47)
  - National - 1972 (Box 47)
  - National - Current Focus (Box 47)
  - National - National Voter (Box 47)
  - National - Program, 1942-1945 (Box 47)
  - National - Program-Making, 1961-1973. 4 Folders. (Box 47)
  - National - Publications and Memoranda, 1965-1969 (Box 48)
  - National – Report from the Hill (Box 49)
  - National - Tips on Reaching the Public (Box 49)
  - Neighborhood Government (Box 49)
  - New Voter Program (Box 49)
  - New York City - Board of Elections (Box 49)
  - New York City - Budget, 1955-196U (Box 49)
  - New York City - Charter, 1934-1938, 1961-1966 1970-1973. 3 Folders (Box 49)
  - New York City - Council, 1939, 1947, 1960-1969 1973. 2 Folders (Box 50)
  - New York City - Health and Hospitals, 1929-1930 (Box 50)
  - New York State Legislation, 1973 (Box 50)
  - New York Votes (Coalition) 1971 (Box 50)
  - Nominating Committee, 1964-1966 1971-1972. 2 Folders (Box 50)
  - Observer, 1971-1972 (Box 50)
  - Office Space, 1971-1973 (Box 50)
  - Organization, 1949-1956 (Box 50)
  - Organizations, Other (Box 50)
  - Overseas Education Fund (Box 50)
  - Outlook for Work - Election Law, 1962 (Box 50)
  - Pensions, 1934, 1939 (Box 50)
  - Permanent June Primary, 1961 (Box 50)
  - Permanent Personal Registration, 1920-1963 (Box 50)
  - 1920-1949 (Box 51)
  - 1949-1955 (Box 52)
  - 1951-1960 (Box 53)
  - 1953-1963 (Box 54)
  - Permanent Personal Registration - Cost Lists (Box 55)
  - Permanent Personal Registration - Methods and Tactics (Box 55)
  - Permanent Personal Registration - Statements (Box 55)
  - Permanent Personal Registration - Printed and miscellaneous (Box 55)
  - Police Review Board (Box 55)
  - Policies and Procedures (Box 55)
  - Political Accountability (Box 55)
  - Politics in Action, 1973 (Box 55)
  - Practical Politics, 1951-1955 196O-1961+. 2 Folders (Box 55)
  - Presidency, U.S. (Box 55)
  - Presidential Elections (Box 55)
  - President's Mailing, Duplicate, 1964-1968 (Box 55)
  - 1964-1965 (Box 56)
  - 1966 (Box 57)
  - 1966 (Box 58)
  - 1966-1968 (Box 59)
  - Press Book, 1969-1970 (Box 60)
  - Program, 1930-1939, 1948-1949 (SEE ALSO Current Agenda and Continuing Responsibilities (Box 60)
  - Program-Making, Local, 1973 (Box 60)
  - Programs and Meetings, 1920-1929 and n.d. (Box 60)
  - Programs and Meetings, 1930-1939 (Box 60)
  - Programs and Meetings, 1940-1949 (Box 60)
  - Programs and Meetings, Area Conference, 1950 (Box 60)
  - Programs and Meetings, Citywide Meeting, 1951 (Box 60)
  - Programs and Meetings, 1951, 1952, 1962 (Box 60)
  - Programs and Meetings, Citywide Meetings, 1952 (Box 60)
  - Programs and Meetings, Area Conferences, 1952-1953 (Box 60)
  - Programs and Meetings, Citywide Meeting, 1955 (Box 60)
  - Programs and Meetings - Brooklyn Candidates, 1963 (Box 61)
  - Programs and Meetings, 1964-1967 (Box 61)
  - Programs and Meetings, 1970-1974 (Box 61)
  - Proportional Representation - SEE Apportionment (Box 61)
  - Public Finance - General (Box 61)
  - Public Finance - Budgets (Box 61)
  - Public Finance - Inflation Control (Box 61)
  - Public Relations (includes news releases), 1935-1951, 1953-1962 1963-1970. 3 Folders (Box 61)
  - Public Relations, 1971-1979 (Box 62)
  - Publications - General (Box 62)
  - Publications - 1969, 1970 (Box 62)
  - Publications - 1971, 1973 (Box 62)
  - Reapportionment - SEE Apportionment (Box 62)
  - Redistricting " (Box 62)
  - Reorganization, 1955-1956 (Box 62)
  - Report Forms (Box 63)
  - Reports on Programs and Activities (SEE ALSO Annual Reports), 1930-1945, 1948 (Box 63)
  - Reports on Programs and Activities (SEE ALSO Annual Reports), 1935-1946. 6 Folders (Box 63)
  - Reports and Announcements, Mimeographed (SEE ALSO Presidents Mailing) 1937-1952. (Box 63)
  - Reports and Announcements, Mimeographed, 1953-1970 and n.d (Box 63)
  - Reports and Announcements, Mimeographed, 1971-1974 (Box 64)
  - Representative Government, 1973 (Box 64)
  - School Health Services, New York City (Box 64)
  - Second Suffrage, 1968 (Box 64)
  - Social Welfare and Child Welfare (Box 64)
  - Social Welfare - Youth Services Council (Box 64)
  - Spanish Language "Facts for Voters" (Box 64)
  - Speakers Kits, 1950-1965. 2 Folders (Box 64)
  - Speakers Kits, 1966-1971 (Box 65)
  - Special Gifts, 1971-1973. 3 Folders (Box 65)
  - Spring Seminars, 1972-1973. 2 Folders (Box 65)
  - State (i.e., League of Women Voters of New York State) - Minutes, 1921 – 1936 (Box 66-68)
  - State - Minutes, 1937 – 1947 (Box 69)
  - State - Minutes, 1948-1959 (Box 70)
  - State - Annual Reports, 1921-1959 (Box 71)
  - State - Council, 1939-1964 (Box 72)
  - State - Conventions, 1935-1953 (Box 73)
  - State - Conventions, 1955-1959 (Box 74)
  - State - Conventions, 1971-1973 (Box 75)
  - State - Conventions, Legislative Conferences, 1941-1959 (Box 75)
  - State - Conventions, Board Reports, 1965-1971 (Box 75)
  - State - General Files, 1940-1971 (Box 76)
  - State - Apportionment (Box 76)
  - State - ByLaws (Box 76)
  - State - Education (Box 76)
  - State - Election Law (Box 76)
  - State - Finances (Box 76)
  - State - Judiciary (Box 76)
  - State - New York State Voter (Box 77)
  - State - Primaries (SEE ALSO Election Law) (Box 77)
  - State - Program-Making, I965-I967 (Box 77)
  - State - 1969-1971 (Box 77)
  - State - 1973 (Box 77)
  - State - Publications (Box 77)
  - State - Voters Service (Box 77)
  - State - Workbooks (Box 77)
  - Statements, Public and Policy (Box 78)
  - Staten Island Community College (Box 78)
  - Structure Committee, 1969 (Box 78)
  - Student Activities (Box 78)
  - Subway Fare, 1935-1947 (Box 78)
  - Summer Workshops, 1971, 1972 1973. 3 Folders (Box 78)
  - Survey Committee, 1961-I963 (Box 78)
  - Tax Exemption, 1923-1947 (Box 79)
  - Techniques (Speakers, Trainers, etc.) (Box 79)
  - Television Programs, 196O-1962 (SEE ALSO Direct Line and "You're It.. ."' (Box 79)
  - Trade, 1954-1973. 3 Folders. (Box 79)
  - Trade - Poll, 1954 (Box 80)
  - Trade - Publications (Box 80)
  - Transportation, 1972-1973 (Box 80)
  - Travel, 1973 (Box 80)
  - Tri-State Committee, 1970-1973. 2 Folders (Box 80)
  - United Nations, 1950-1970 (Box 80)
  - United Nations, 1970-1971 (Box 8l)
  - United States Constitution (Box 8l)
  - Urban Action, 1972-1973 (Box 8l)
  - Utilities, Public (Box 8l)
  - Veterans Bonus (Box 8l)
  - Visitors, 1972 (Box 8l)
  - Vote Power (Box 8l)
  - "Voteman° (Box 8l)
  - Voter Registration (Box 8l)
  - Voter Qualifications (Box 8l)
  - Voter Service, 1950-1996 (Box 8l)
  - 1950-1959 (Box 82 and 82a)
  - 1960-1963 (Box 83)
  - 1964 (Box 84)
  - 1965-1966 (Box 85)
  - Voters Service, 1966-1967 Primary Poll Watching Project (Box 86)
  - Voters Service, 1968-1973. 2 Folders (Box 87)
  - WABC, 1972 (Box 87)
  - WCBS, 1971-1972 (Box 87)
  - War Activities, 1934-1942 1947-2 Folders (Box 87)
  - Water Resources, 1955-1962. 2 Folders (Box 87)
  - Water Resources, 1963-1967 (Box 88)
  - Water Resources, 1968-1970 (Box 89)
  - Water Resources, Delaware River Basin. 2 Folders (Box 89)
  - Water Resources, Lake Erie Basin (Box 89)
  - Water Resources, Ohio River Basin (Box 89)
  - Water Resources, Pollution Abatement Campaign, 1965 (Box 89)
  - Water Resources, Susquehanna (Box 89)
  - Water Resources, Slides. 8 Boxes (Box 89)
  - Welfare, 1935-1971 (Box 90)
  - Woman Suffrage (Box 90)
  - Womens’ Africa Committee (Box 90)
  - Workplans, 1956-1967 (Box 90)
  - Workshops and Seminars (Box 90)
  - "You’re It — You Are Government, USA" 1951-1952 (Box 90)
  - Youth In Politics (Box 90)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 90)
  - Printed Materials (primarily pamphlets; some mimeographs and clippings) (Box 91-100)
  - Photographs (Box 101)
  - Scrapbooks, (6 volumes) (Box 135-136)
  - Oversize material: 2 Folders: Proclamations of League of Women Voters Day, 1958 and 1959. (Box Mapcase 14-P-01)
- Series III: 1990 Addition
  - Action-Annual Reports (Box 102)
  - Bicentennial-Charter revisions (Box 103)
  - City Conventions-Community Development (Box 104)
  - Conference of Urban Problems-Conventions (Box 105)
  - Correspondence (1979-1981)-Council Kit Contents (Box 106)
  - Cultural Affairs-Finance (Box 107)
  - Foundation for City Education-Litigation (Box 108)
  - Martin’s Department Store-Memoranda (Box 109)
  - Memoranda (cont.)-Munites (Box 110)
  - National Leangue (1961-1968)-New School Spring Seminar, 1972 (Box 111)
  - News Clippings-"N" Miscellaneous (Box 112)
  - Operating Manuals-Radio (Box 113)
  - Radio (cont.)-United Nations Background Material (Box 114)
  - United Nations (cont.)-Voting Machine (Spanish Film) (Box 115)
  - "What Makes N.Y.C. Run?" – Women’s Issues (Box 116)
  - Women's Job Rights Proposal - Year of Young Voter (Box 117)
  - Photographic Material - Miscellaneous Papers (Box ll8)
  - Foreign Economic Policy: Action Calls (Box 119)
  - Foreign Economic Policy: Congressional Role Call Votes (Box 119)
  - Foreign Economic Policy: Correspondence(1963-1964) (Box 120)
  - Foreign Economic Policy: Field Trips (1955-1975) (Box 120)
  - Foreign Economic Policy: Foreign Aid Statements (Box 121)
  - Foreign Economic Policy: Publications (Old) (Box 121)
  - Foreign Economic Policy: Scrapbook (Box 122)
  - Foreign Economic Policy: World Trade (Box 122)
  - Printed Material (Box 123-134)